Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going. Go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther.
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
Live out another day so intense.
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead.
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
Running forever. Open the map inside your
heart and see. No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams and you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
Go, the Straw Hats.
Black-Legged Sanji, right?
Diablo Jamba!
Premier Hachi's head!
Penta-chromatic strength!
Hachi's head! But how?
You don't have the strength
to protect anybody!
He's headed right for us!
What are we going to do?
Don't you dare turn your back
on me, or my Boa Hancock.
Well, I'm pre-respecting.
He's not bad.
What?
I can't move.
What the hell's happening to me?
Strange.
It looks like something's
holding Sanji still in mid-air.
That's the young master's power.
There's no hope of escape for your friend.
Blacklegs captured.
As helpless as a fly in a spider's web.
All he can do now is
hope for a quick death.
What is that? A whip?
What the hell are you waiting around for?
Use a coup to burst and go!
We're not leaving you!
Over here!
Sanji!
It's time to break free!
Shambles!
The room!
Oh, damn it!
Run!
Sanji!
We've changed Sanji's life!
There's been a slight change of plans.
To the ship!
A ten-point landing.
Glad you...
Don't tell me I'm back on
this cursed ship again!
Oh, Caesar!
Is that you, Giolla?
Break me free!
I would love to, but I'm
a little tied up myself!
That won't happen again.
The flamingos come back for round two!
Wait, Blackleg!
How are things going with the factory?
We found out where it is.
But Franky says it's gonna be tougher
to take down than we first thought.
And my father?
Was he able to rescue Kanjiro safely?
Please tell me that all is well!
Kinemon's friend is at the factory.
If we pull this off, he'll be saved.
We still need more time,
you bastard that isn't.
my heart is it so you were keeping it back
here in the ship cabin
i'm afraid this one's
mine I had, yours with me,
never left my side? Ah?
Trickery.
All my plans thwarted by
one miserable little lie.
Listen up.
Here's the plan.
I want you to head to
Zoe and take him. To Zoe?
I gave you the Vivre card that
leads to the next island already.
We're leaving already?
What are we supposed to do
about Luffy and the others?
There is only one task left
that remains on this island.
Destroying the factory.
As soon as we're done, we'll
catch up with you guys.
We're not going anywhere yet.
If you think we're going to set sail
without our captain, you're nuts.
We take orders from Luffy, not you.
There's a Navy battleship
flying right over us!
How close is that even possible?
It must be Fujitora.
The flamingo's closing
it from the other side!
You can wait for Straw Hat if you like.
But you have to guard Caesar.
Fire!
Big rocks are falling out of the sky!
Are those meteors? Crew!
As a senior member of the Straw Hat
crew, I vote that we get out of here now!
I second that motion! Then
get moving! Hold up, Law.
I realize it's important to get Caesar
as far away from here as possible.
And it's pretty obvious
we have to leave him now.
But the operation in Dressrosa was
just supposed to be a waypoint.
I thought our shared goal was taking
down Kaido of the Four Emperors.
I wonder why are you getting
so hung up on Doflamingo?
Meteors! Did you forget? Tucked!
Iso, they managed to
put a hole in the bilge!
Law's on the ship below us, isn't he?
It was mighty careless of
me to overlook that fact.
Why are you still eating
in a time like this?
What should we do, sir?
I've got a premonition.
The battle's taking a turn.
Turn the boat around.
There's no escape.
A whip again. Great.
Joker, get me off of this boat.
Overheat.
Nami, look for a spot without any clouds
and set sail for it now. What? But why?
Because Doflamingo has the
powers of the string fruit.
He moves through the air by
attaching strings to clouds.
A clear sky means he can't chase you.
I see.
Well, that explains a lot.
What are you waiting around for?
Who did burst fire?
Doflamingo!
Eyes over here!
Locke, how could you do this?
Don't worry about me, young master.
You can't let them escape!
What's the point of letting
half the Straw Hats escape?
Aren't you forgetting something?
The rest of them are still in dress rosa.
All i have to do is take them
hostage and the ones who ran
off will sail right back and
offer me caesar for their release.
How many people have underestimated
them and gotten burned?
You really want to add
your name to that list?
At any rate,
my pirate alliance with the straw hag
crew is coming to its natural conclusion.
Do i have to spell it out for
you from the moment we teamed up?
My only goal was shutting
down the smile factory.
I was using them, and while killing
you today would bring me pleasure.
Sure, it doesn't matter, since
Kaido will do it sooner or later.
after you end up losing the smiles.
How noble of you.
Sacrificing your life to stop me.
Well, I'd love to see what chaos the
world falls into once you're dead.
First and foremost, I want to make
you pay for what you did 13 years ago.
Joker!
Come on, Law.
Holding Gyula hostage won't
get you anywhere with me.
He's got a point.
I'll gladly give my life for
the sake of the young master.
And I'd advise you to run away.
Yes, sir!
Things got messy back on Straw Hat's ship.
I admit my plan isn't going
quite as smoothly as I'd hoped.
My, you are still mad.
Grudges aren't healthy.
I'd let it go.
This isn't just a grudge.
I've lived my whole life
to achieve this goal.
I'll see his dream through to the end!
I sure hope Trappy's okay.
Pay attention, you guys.
See anything out there?
Brooke reporting here.
At a 45-degree angle,
everything looks just lovely.
If he comes near us again, then I'll use
my weapon to blow away all the clouds.
He won't be able to follow us.
You better protect my sweet Robin,
even if it costs you your lives.
You got that?
What's up?
I was making sure that Robin's still
safe—she's with Franky and Usopp right now.
Okay, so if Zoro and Kin'emon meet
up with Luffy, we should be fine!
Well,
Mosshead's probably too bad with directions
to find his way to the Coliseum alone.
But
Kinemon's with him, so they'll make
it—I'm awful worried about Trafi though?
trafi though
Eh, he's a big boy.
Seems he's planning to let Kaido kill
Doflamingo instead of offing the guy himself.
So he just has to focus
on escaping now. Yeah.
Yeah.
Hey, why'd you turn back into a dragon?
I...
I just can't stop thinking
about what happened.
That flying man.
Doflamingo?
Yes, I remember seeing him the
last time I came to Dressrosa.
Really?
Master, you're gonna kill him!
What the hell's the matter with you?
You're supposed to be a gladiator, right?
Then act like it.
A gladiator should fight for his life,
not run around like a chicken
with its head cut off.
So if you can't bring
yourself to kill anyone,
the least you can do is let
somebody cut you to pieces.
Don't act like you don't know;
all humans are the same—everyone gets
riled up over a little bloodshed,
and that's why they're here.
Sorry, that's just an attainment
now. Entertain! Entertain! Hey!
Piece of garbage.
Better not see anyone else
cutting corners. Yes, sir!
Kinemo, there you are.
Uh, it's Kanjudo.
I found a harbor.
We have to steal a ship and escape.
This land is too dangerous.
I just realized that foul monster
is holding Conis captive as we speak
and now i simply cannot stop worrying
please be safe
Conjure all. Why do you
look so happy don't worry being taken
hostage is no big deal whatever they
wanted out of him i'm sure they won't
torture him too bad He'll be okay,
you're obviously thinking
about something else at least
pretend to care that reminds me
violet said she'd be okay, too
I'll be fine.
I talked to my friend, and I'm
certain the government will protect me
Really?
Yes, they're probably
waiting for me at the harbor.
All right, I'd feel better if I could
go along with you as long as you're safe
You've done enough.
I can do this thanks to all your help.
How can I ever show my gratitude?
Well, we could start with a little
kiss on the cheek, and then maybe...
Oh, no!
It would seem your sheep is
under attack by fighting fish!
Uh-oh. What are those? No time! Just go!
Nami!
Damnit!
She's still alive!
How'd she get this far?
Mr. Horse? Yes?
Take me to the palace, quickly!
You got it!
What's got you so upset
now, whatever weirdo?
Tell me why you know so
much about me and Luffy!
I've been your biggest fan for years.
Ugh, so pathetic—you can't even answer!
Could
I could I have your autograph?
I said it.
it What?
If I bring Mr.
Luffy to you, then will
you give me your autograph?
It'd be a big help if you did.
Well, come on. Hop to it.
Oh, oh, oh, what? Oh, then wait.
Wait, wait there.
I'll bring Mr.
Luffy back here if it kills me.
It's not that serious.
She just won't quit!
That's her favorite move!
It's come to be known as
the back-to-the-water dance!
You must grow stronger to survive, child.
Taking advantage of her enemy's momentum,
she lures them to the edge of the ring
and stands with her back to the water!
Finally,
she dodges her opponent's
defenses with lightning speed,
causing them to barrel
right into the vault!
Yes, because of that technique,
despite fighting in countless battles.
Rebecca has never once wounded anybody.
She uses observation Haki sweet Haki.
Rebecca's also never been
wounded during a match.
So far, she's won every fight just by
letting her foes fall off the side.
Whoa!
What a trooper!
Good job, Rebecca!
Remarkable fighting style, even
if she's hardly fighting at all!
I must grudgingly admit, there's
something beautiful about it.
Still, it may define its
match in this competition.
The other warriors have their own unique
ways of eliminating their opponents.
They are world-class gladiators.
Huh?
Lucky me.
Now I get to pulverize you.
Let's get this going, little weed.
Next patient, Mr.
Sai from the Kano Kingdom.
What about the last patient?
You carried our old man back there
and haven't said a stinking word.
You mean Mr. Qin Zhao?
If he ain't dead, then what gives?
Huh?
Jeez.
Shut your trap.
Nobody cares.
I know he's getting old,
so it's no surprise.
Just give me the truth. If the man's dead,
you're supposed to tell the next of kin.
Can you keep it down?
You're overreacting sir.
The situation's not nearly
as dramatic as all that.
There's an exit in the back
of the infirmary After you
get treated you don't come
back to the waiting room.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I made such a big scene over nothing
Well, glad we cleared
it up now, please go in
No, you don't understand.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
I feel terrible for
putting you on the spot
I'm on my knees, asking, begging you
for your forgiveness. Don't worry.
He's just a little emotional.
He'll get over it
Um, okay.
Just lie down on the bed
here and we'll get started
Like this?
Yes, and you'll need to close your eyes
All right, commencing examination
Oh, what the hell?
Send in the next one.
What is this stuff?
Bunch of dolls?
Looks like a trash heap.
Made of of toys and fighters.
Who's there?
You?
Hyrudin?
all you guys
what the hell is this place
you're alive well that's
good news I'm happy
what part about any of this is good news
you idiot my guess is if you lose the
tournament you're chucked thrown out with the
trash thrown out what does that mean how
are we gonna get out
of here there is no way
out we were set up by
that bastard Doflamingo
This is an act of war.
Our king is a bellow!
Hate to say it, but even my
king, Punch, can't break us out.
You realize we're underground, right?
Which means these walls are solid earth.
Of course your technique
doesn't work, idiot.
We're all strong, and none of
our techniques will get us out.
What's their endgame here?
Are they collecting fighters or what?
Whatever it is, I doubt they
plan on tending to our wounds.
I will curse you for
this offense, Doflamingo!
I'll curse your children
and grandchildren too!